Good morning guys.  Happy
Independence Day to everyone.  So today we all are going to
Papa's school from where Papa did his schooling.  Get the
full Independence Day vibe going with this
cute Chocopie pack for kids.
Carrying all the weight on my shoulders, I went out.  And you
can see the weather outside.  It was becoming so cute.  While
acting as an independent woman, I had reached there.  Everyone had
reached and sat in the car and after this
we ate white sauce pasta.  Mom had packed it.  It was getting
so tasty.
Looking at the flags on the car.  My
sister Kaleshi said something useful.
This tricolor is currently visible in everyone's vehicles and homes.
Tomorrow it will be found somewhere
in the mud, lying somewhere.  I have put
this on just for today.
I too got scared after seeing the anger of this lizard.
Then we put up badges giving the whole vibe and it was
so much fun to see the mini tiny kids from the schools in the rally.  Then we
reached there laughing and playing.  Papa's name was
also announced here.  Then there was flank hosting and the
national anthem.  The children sang some patriotic songs.
Papa was showing his
classes where he had taught earlier.
And the vibe here was so cool and aesthetic, was
n't it?  These mini tiny kids turned out to be my fans too.
Then we went to the hall where the
entire celebration started.  Papa
got these special batches there.  Hum Hum after that
all the programs started.  All
patriotic songs and dances.  Bhuvi enjoyed the
tea.  We used to enjoy the programs.
My sister Kalesh got angry here too and
because of Kalesh she got us expelled
from the school.  Then we all went to eat momos
and had a lot of fun, guys.  Happy
Independence Day to everyone today.  Bye-bye.